http://www.jasco.com/privacy-data-protection-policy

Privacy & Data Protection
JASOC’s privacy and data protection policy: when, why, and how we might store and process employee and client information. Including how we meet the requirements of the European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and the Canadian Personal Information Protection and Electronics Document Act (PIPEDA).
/
Home/
About/
About JASCO
Mission & Values
Quality — ISO 9001
Leadership Team
Health, Safety & Environment
Download JASCO Brochure
More BrochuresPrivacy & Data Protection PolicyOur Commitment to Privacy and Data ProtectionWe are committed to protecting the rights and interests of our employees and our clients, so we have in place a privacy and data protection policy that meets stringent international practices including the requirements of the European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and the Canadian Personal Information Protection and Electronics Document Act (PIPEDA).We shall always inform individuals when we store and process their personal data, ensuring they understand what data we store and process, with whom we share it, and why. We accomplish this through communication of this policy to our stakeholders both internal and external and any further communications required by the GDPR and PIPEDA.Employee InformationWe shall only store and process personal data when we have a lawful basis to do so and only for the core business purposes of staff administration, marketing, advertising, public relations, accounting, and record keeping. The sensitivity of the data we store and process and the impact of such storage and processing on individuals will be carefully balanced against the legitimate interests of JASCO to ensure the rights and interests of the individuals are protected.We shall share personal information only if there is a lawful basis for doing so, only for core business purposes, and only with individual consent, when applicable. Before any exchange of personal data takes place, we shall ensure that those with whom we share information have themselves a privacy policy that meets the requirements of the GDPR and PIPEDA.Client InformationWe shall only store and process client personal information provided directly by current or past clients during business transactions. We shall only store and process the minimal information required to contact clients regarding products and services they have received from JASCO or may wish to receive from JASCO in the future, or to enable the delivery of services. We shall not share this information with a third party without client consent. Clients have the right to contact JASCO (see below) at any time to disallow the use of their data for specific purposes or in absolute.Automated Data ProcessingWe shall not perform automated processing or mining of personal data.Compliance ReviewsWe shall regularly review the personal data that we store and process, and associated consent records, to ensure that they are accurate and up to date and that they still need to be retained. We shall regularly review our data handling controls, data sharing controls, records management controls, and security controls, as well as this policy, to ensure continued compliance with the GDPR and PIPEDA.ConsentWe shall seek individual consent as the requisite lawful basis to store and process personal data, as applicable, and shall inform individuals of their rights under the GDPR and PIPEDA as follows.Right to be informedIndividuals have the right to know what personal data we are collecting, how and why we are processing it, and with whom we are sharing it.Right of accessIndividuals have the right to obtain a copy of their personal data in our possession at any time.Right of rectification and data qualityIndividuals have the right to ensure that their information in our possession is correct and complete.Right to erasure including retention and disposalIndividuals have the right to request secure disposal of their personal data from our records at any time.Right to restrict processingIndividuals have the right to restrict processing of their personal data.Right to objectIndividuals have the right to object to the processing of their data.Contacting JASCOIndividuals may contact privacy@jasco.com at any time to exercise any of their rights above or to request further information or clarification regarding this policy. Such requests will be addressed within one calendar month of receipt.
Back to Home
For more information, contact your nearest JASCO office:CanadaHalifax, NSJASCO Applied Sciences (Canada) Ltd202–32 Troop AvenueDartmouth, NS  B3B 1Z1 Canada Tel:  +1-902-405-3336Fax: +1-902-405-3337halifax@jasco.comVictoria, BCJASCO Applied Sciences (Canada) Ltd2305–4464 Markham Street Victoria, BC  V8Z 7X8  CanadaTel:  +1-250-483-3300 Fax: +1-250-483-3301 victoria@jasco.comUnited StatesSilver Spring, MDJASCO Applied Sciences (USA) Inc.8630 Fenton Street, Suite 218Silver Spring, MD 20910 USATel: +1-301-565-3500maryland@jasco.comEuropeUnited KingdomJASCO Applied Sciences (UK) LtdThe Roundel, St Clair’s FarmWickham Road, DroxfordHampshire SO32 3PWUnited KingdomTel: +44 (0) 1489 878439europe@jasco.comGermanyJASCO Applied Sciences (Deutschland) GmbHMergenthaler Allee 15-2165760 EschbornDeutschlandeurope@jasco.comAustraliaQueenslandJASCO Applied Sciences (Australia) Pty Ltd14 Hook Street, Unit 1Capalaba QLD 4157AustraliaTel: +61 7 3823 2620 australia@jasco.com
Copyright © JASCO Applied Sciences. All rights reserved.
